<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thesis on Marco Console Personal Page</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/thesis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thesis on Marco Console Personal Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This is a customized copyright.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/thesis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Curiculum Vitae Highlights</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cv/</guid>
      <description>Apointments From 2022 to date: Ricercatore a Tempo Determinato di Categoria B (Tenured Assistant Professor). Dipartimento di Ingegneria Informatica, Automatica e Gestionale. Sapienza, University of Rome From 2020 to 2022: Ricercatore a Tempo Determinato di Categoria A (Non-Tenured Assistant Professor). Dipartimento di Ingegneria Informatica, Automatica e Gestionale. Sapienza, University of Rome From 2016 to 2020: Research Associate. School of Informatics. University of Edinburgh. From 2013 to 2016: Phd Student in Engineering in Computer Science Dipartimento di Ingegneria Informatica, Automatica e Gestionale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student Projects and Thesis Work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/theses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/theses/</guid>
      <description>Part of my role as a teacher involves supervising student projects and thesis work. I greatly value this activity as it allows me to collaborate closely with students, guiding them as they apply their knowledge, develop new skills, and contribute to meaningful research. Additionally, a research-oriented thesis is also a great opportunity to build enough knowledge to start a PhD.&#xA;Possible topics to explore together are the following (in no particular order):</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
